And I will call the order of the modest, special utility authority board meeting for Monday, March 6th, 2023, and we'll have the implication from Deputy Fire Chief, the Modify Department, Mr. Great General.
Heavenly Father, we're thankful for you in the way you love us. What a beautiful day this was and the statuses we go through this meeting that the discussion is respectful and honest.
Now you'd be with our council members and give them guidance as they make their decisions. It's in your name we pray. Amen.
Budget allegiance to the fire of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God, and you're visible with liberty and justice for all.
For public input runs scheduled personal appearances.
Five consent agenda.
Staff recommends we approve item six and seven.
Eight budget amendments moving money from the IT budget to the grant donation fund to cover over expenditures on CESF.
Number 20E128 grant for computer equipment and receiving an expending insurance for every money is to replace a damaged pole.
I would thank you for taking it back to you.
The number of paying for polls for dollars.
Hello.
So as you'd read, we have the transferring IT funds from the IT budget to the grant donation fund and then also we are doing your taking me insurance recovery check that we received and transferring
during the budget transfer for about four of the expenses that were incurred for the damage.
Well, I would say that the grant.
That's a lot of money.
But one of my short parts.
I'd give.
I'd like a motion to approve.
Thank you.
Good.
El Stratton.
Edmund Palmer Claim for Jared A.
relaxing thing in the amount of $12,719.
50 cents.
So mayors and council.
This is a.
This is for good El Stratton for services for
$12,719.
So we've got $520,719.
So that's for your approval for this $520,719.
For $12,719.
10 update on Oklahoma Water Resource Board.
Our boat grant for $619.
So if you remember, after you mentioned,
we came before the MSUA Board for a.
Resolution to approve.
So many our application to our boat.
Or the water grant.
And we're happy to say that we were.
We're worth two million dollars for our grant.
So yes, so we had.
I like the thing.
You know what?
So.
John.
Robin.
Good.
Jeff.
So we all.
We all went together.
We wrote this grant.
And I'm happy to say we score 59 priority points.
We tied us with two other cities for the highest ranking project.
With the whole state.
So we're excited about it.
We call off the triangle out there on 690.
It's a triangle area.
Right there.
That's where our water terrors are going to go.
And it'll be like a tea that goes in there.
Sorry.
Yeah.
And so we'll put it there.
And then we're trying to have it up money to have a water line that goes underneath the
Turnpike and feeds the pool of your housing.
So currently they only have one way to get water.
You know, every, we're also the system.
We try to have two feeds.
So we'll loop feed systems.
So if we do a helicopter on one side, we can give them water from the other side.
Well, we repair it.
So that's there.
We're going to look to do that.
So we're excited.
They call me in like 15 and 9 today.
Congratulations.
You guys have been awarded the grant.
Can't let anybody know.
So I took a few weeks before they allowed us to tell everybody.
So.
Thank you.
59 priority points.
That was the highest anybody got. I don't know for sure what their ranking was. So in your packet, there's a ranking.
So we'll be coming back. We'll put the water tower off her bed and the other water lines to go on with it.
We'll put it off her bed and we'll come back to the machine board for approval.
And we'll submit to whatever it be for approval. And we'll actually have the table.
We'll actually have like a celebration we get to go to.
So in the two of you are a total cost of the project.
No, we have, we're matching that you made.
You know, we have money already. Some of the money already set aside for.
So we borrow, you know, but with the precovers and what the price is never going to go into.
We're excited about it. Something that the city definitely needs.
So if any information on 6 to 9 A, we can go for that.
We're excited.
We can be blue.
Tell me, I want to congratulate you.
You've been coming to do that.
Thank you. I know that was like, I don't know.
I don't know.
That's a proper turn.
We're excited about it.
We're going.
So all those extra things cost lots of money to do.
We're not came across that much.
I think.
I don't want one of the kids to go out to the planet.
You know, they all told me he's great.
Yeah.
I think.
I think they go. They told me like I wanted to paint a checkered because everyone's
why you see like checkered water dollar. They're looking beautiful.
And I think they said that cost an extra $1,000.
Plus, you're the one that messaged me one time.
I wanted to have a fancy painted water tower.
Actually, I had a resident.
I just poured the question to you.
So then I asked.
Yeah.
I think our water tower here used to be.
Checked.
What?
Yeah.
I believe it did.
That's right.
I don't know.
What's your balance?
I think the one out further down by the mushroom plant.
I don't think like a mushroom.
Okay.
So you done with that one?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Number 11.
Project closed up.
Change order on contract C21-56.
The circle will be underground for highway six on eight.
Sanctuary zero project C19-2021 slash ORF-14-001-CW.
not to exceed $20,000, contingent on Oklahoma Water Research Board of Representatives.
So this is the close-out of the 69A sewer line that we did.
I had to talk about quantities and different things.
So the Proctor of Project was 2.5.
Man 2.4.
Man, it's an air packet.
And the contractor installed a little bit more of a deeper depth of the sewer,
a little less of the shallower depth.
So fast for the additional money.
Yes, sir.
And John, it's in your packet is the additional reductions.
We were trying to get me the packet deadline and then also get their change over back from.
So the amount you're proving is $15,000.
They will be in the latest, I met with them last week.
And we went through and reviewed all the images of all the infrastructure they built out there.
And specifically, all the infrastructure they built out there that cannot use yet.
So they're very anxious to get this completed in a lot of this.
Full utilized, dirty bathrooms and facilities.
I like the motion to prove the $15,000, $13,000 and $3,000 change order from C21-56.
Thank you.
Twelve, any other new business, which has had residents of the posting of this agenda?
13 staff reports, 14 trustee community announcements, 15 adjournment.
Bye.